{
    "id": "840ebf0ef548480ba7c97fb20a88687c",
    "title": "Simple Past Or Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His father ...................... last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "has died",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e08aa99df79648c88554bec4a17e5b04"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. an apple in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat",
                "ate",
                "have eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efac724f962b41ba9cc79bbe3b9e7754"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… working on that report yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not finish",
                "have not finished",
                "not finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d768c09ab96a41ecae28f6a0e63550ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ....................... to America last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "gone",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20b30b58182347ac9ae12e8069e9e0eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................... a hamburger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never eat",
                "never ate",
                "have never eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aa75b3e5c1a94713a7b600b6ab1e980b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ...................... 12 chocolates since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ate",
                "have eaten",
                "had eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46224037b7aa4aa4ac72292f76b9e0db"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ..................... in this city since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lived",
                "have lived",
                "had lived"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db81d2852c264078b86936b9c6b5576b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... John last week and we .....................… his plans.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met, discussed",
                "have met, have discussed",
                "had met, had discussed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2bbdf7366fa4471982f44e6dfabcf58c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. the parcel yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not receive",
                "have not received",
                "had not received"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c11e1ab0d954a908a00fbf54b46555b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… the parcel in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "receive",
                "received",
                "have received"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "892e4c98951a47ac9e3a1fc772225b3b"
        }
    ]
}